Prasuk Jain

Software Development Intern

Enthusiastic Web-developer with the deep interest in creating visually enriched web experience. Skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. Passionate in learning Data Structures and Algorithms. Experienced in C/C++ and Git. Strong hold on Communication skills and Management skills with a B.Tech. focused in Electronics and Communication Engineering.

prasukjain0047@gmail.com	\geq
--------------------------	--------

+91 62658-57985

Indore, India

coderprasukj.github.io/PortFolio/

linkedin.com/in/prasukjain04 in

github.com/coderprasukj

EDUCATION

B.Tech. Electronics and Communication Shri G.S. Institute of Technology and Science

2018 – Present

Indore. India

12th

New Shanti Niketan Higher Secondary School

2016 - 2018

Vidisha, India

10th

St. Mary's Convent Sr. Sec. School

2004 - 2016

Bhopal, India

PERSONAL PROJECTS

 A responsive interactive website to display my technical skills. Developed with using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

My Code Class

 A learning platform for computer science enthusiast with an attractive user-interface developed with HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Campus Ambassdor GeeksforGeeks

05/2020 - Present Achievements/Tasks

 Motivated students to write technical articles on Company's website and take courses for developing their skills.

Open Source Contributor GirlScript Summer of Code

03/2020 - 05/2020

Achievements/Tasks

 Worked on a Forked Repository of Data Structures and Algorithms in GirlScript Summer of Code 2020.

SKILLS

ACHIEVEMENTS

CodeChef: coderprasukj 🗹

Secured Global Rank 379 in Exun Programming Prelims'19 held on CodeChef. Secured Global Rank 963 in October Mega Cook-off'19 on Codechef.

Facebook HackerCup'20

Cleared Qualification Round and Advanced to Round 1.

GirlScript Summer of Code

Contributed and Secured Top 50 Rank in open source projects in GirlScript Summer of Code'20

Webathon

Secured 2nd position in Webathon conducted by Progate at College-Level.

ORGANIZATIONS

Co-Ordinator, CodeFoster (08/2019 – Present)

Have successfully organized coding events, seminars and guiding sessions for students. Managed the Social Handles and Accounts of Club for Interactive Learning.

CERTIFICATES

Data Structures and Algorithms GeeksforGeeks

HTML, CSS and JavaScript for Web Developers

Johns Hopkins University, USA, Coursera

Algorithmic Toolbox

University of California, San Diego

COURSES

Data Structures

Algorithms

Operating System

Digital System Design